(Time Piggy Bank)
Why mom is not home yet?
This way, I can't go out
and play
Doraemon
This is wasting time.
I hate it
It hurts
Got it
Time is precious
Time piggy bank
Save the time you wasted
Save the time?
It's 1:30, right?
Save 30 minutes before mom
comes back
When you say "30 minutes"
push the red button
It's 2:00 now
There are 30 minutes saved in the
piggy bank
Time can be saved
It's about time mom comes back
I'm home
See, she's back
You can go play now
We're going now
Wow...
Shizuka, come play with us
Nobita
I'm study, please wait 10 minutes
for me
Waiting for 10 minutes is wasting
time
Save the 10 minutes
Ah...
Ah, it's time
Sorry to keep you waiting
It's real. Ha, ha
It's 2:30
Have to go now
Why?
Just started to play
Sorry, I have to go to piano lesson
Time saved can be used now
Take out 40 minutes
When say 40 minutes
push the blue button
Ah, back to 2:00
Can play another 40 minutes
This time Nobita do it. Please
Ok...
It's Doraemon's turn
Bye
Didn't you take your time?
I'm back
I'm home
Where did you all go ?
Didn't do your home work before
going out to play
Why can't you keep the promise
you made with mom
Didn't mom always tell you
Finish your home work before play
Mom has taken a long time to
scold
Save the time when she is scolding
Weird
How come it's dark already?
Mom, it's 6:00
Did I talk so long ?
This is terrible
Hurry and make dinner
So busy
I'm hungry
Hope to have dinner soon
Save the time before dinner
Good idea!
Dinner will be ready soon
Dinner is ready
Great
We're going to eat now
How much time did we save?
About 3 hours
What are they talking about?
7:30 start to watch TV
News time
Save the time before 7:30
News is over
Ah? So soon ?
Weird
So interesting. So fun
It's time to sleep
Oh, no. I've not finished my
home work yet
Oh, no. Oh, no
Write the home work
Write my home work
Didn't do it at all
What should I do ?
What should I do?
I'm back
Welcome home
Save the time
Do you want to use it up all at
one time
Weird
It's bright out again
It's only 4:30
I left the company too early
Must go back again
Yh?
Oh, no
Oh, no Oh, no Oh, no
(Main character package machine)
What are you talking about?
Really?
No!
You're going to be on the most
popular TV show
Universe Super Boy?
To be one of the character ?
Nothing, just for the fun of it
Actually, I didn't want to be in, but
CEO of TV station insists for me
to be in it
I can't refuse him
Please ask him not to let me in it
It's ok to just be a associate
character
Because I don't to be an idle
School work is most important to me
Starting 7:00 tonight
You can all come to my house to
watch TV
Channel 21, 7:00
You can see me on TV
If someone was not happy not
being in it
They don't have to come then
Every time when I think of it
It makes me so mad
He always talks big
I'll not go
But he'll be on TV, will he ?
How envy
How envy...
So envy...
Be quiet
When I'm miserable
Don't standing there kidding me
What makes you so miserable?
Well, Suneo is going to be in the
Universe Super Boy
I want to be in a TV show too
Even if just an associate
To be an associate is too small
If you want to be on TV, you
must be a main character
You can't make it
The problem is that I can
Any time I'll be the main character
Don't be kidding
This is
Ah!!
Why ? Why?
Why, every comics has you as
main character
Tell me, tell me
Use the Main Character Package
machine
Main Character Package machine
Not just the comics
TV series, novels, movies...
Anything can use yourself as the
main character
Come, Nobita
You be the character of this fairy tail
Me be the main character?
Only if it's real
Huff)'
Good Now, you are the main
character
I'm so nervous
Ah? Mother of little duck?
To the little duck, Nobita say:
Nobita, why are you so ugly?
What is that? This is not fun at all
Good, then be on the TV
Now, it's news broadcasting
You try it now
This is the news just received
Police has announced the warrant
to bank robberies
The man is violent
Everyone has to be careful
I have enough! Everyone use a
weird way to talk about me
But you're the main character
I don't want to be a main
character like that
How about in the Universe
Super Boy
Nobita be the Universe Super
Boy, I think it's cool
ls it? I'll be the Universe Super Boy
Good, I'll be at Suneo's house to
watch TV
That way, I can show
Suneo something
Jian, Shizuka, are you all going to
Suneo's house?
Yes, I don't want to be thought
we're jealous about him
Hey, welcome you all
Come in please
It's going t start soon
The big show Suneo's in
Universe Super Boy is about to
start
Be quiet, hurry and start it
Hey, be patient
Ah, 5 seconds before broadcasting
(Universe Super Boy)
This week, it's about Lamp shape
UFO attacking earth
It's on ! Look!
That is me. That is me.
Which one ? Which one?
Second one from the left
Disappeared
That is all ?
Not to show again ?
I did mention it
They ask me to be the associate
What so funny?
Because school work is more
important to me
That's why I just promised to be
associate
I know, I know
Suneo, you're so great
You're really on the TV and
showing off
HEY
Don't laugh. It's not funny at all
Don't laugh? How can we not
laughing?
Right, Nobita?
Universe Super Boy's face
It can't be
This, this is
I can't believe this
I'm the century justice messenger
Universe Super Boy
Universe Super Boy is undestroyed
Nobita, what is this ?
Nothing, I didn't want to be in it
CEO of TV station insists for me
to be in it
I can't refuse him
Great
Would you recommend me too ?
Main Character Package machine
is surprisingly powerful
(Mind reading machine)
I'm fulled
Thank you
I'm sorry
The other room is clean now
You can go now
Heysu
Mom works so hard
Can I play like this?
I'm going shopping
The rest is your responsibility now
Don't worry
Mom, mom
What? Nobita
Mom
Are you not feeling well?
Having fever?
Help me to bring me the comics
on the table
Go take it yourself
Mom is busy
I'm sick
Just a small cold
But I want to be childlike
sometimes
Since getting sick
why don't I get really sick?
Mind reading machine
What kind of machine is this?
Mind reading machine, very
convenient
Can take care of patients or
wounded people
Don't have to push button or
give orders
It'll help you do whatever you
want to
That easy. So nice
Put Antena on your head
Think of something
How did you know
I was so thirsty
That way, you can just lay down
A tool to help you be lazy
Never mind, you're noisy
Wait
Why did it do so much?
Forget it, that's fine
So boring
Only if I can watch TV
Ah?
You're so small
yet can do so much
Now, put those cut pieces into
pot
Stir until mixed
There's no show for kids
at this hour
Tesi's room
Get bored watching TV
Feel like have some desert
This is my red bean cake
Only if it's a small cake
Give it back to me
Happy Desert Time is on now
My desert, give it back to me
As long as I thing about it
It will do it
Delicious
My desert
Who did this ?
My stomach is fulled
Wonder if Shizuka's coming?
Coming
What coming
Jian is here too
Bye
How boring
It's all Jian
I feel like beating him up
So, this is 5
Then...
That;s good enough
Shizuka
Ah? Where is Shizuka ?
Who are you?
It hurts, what are you doing?
Sorry, when I realise it I was at
Nobita's house
No, you must come in person
Never mind that. No.
Really, how embarrassing
Tired of sleeping
The cold is gone
Go and play
It's been a long time to breath
the fresh air
Walk around the neighborhood
Ah?
Jian, what happened to yours face
Suneo ?
Let me tell you, my face..
I slept all day long
Just half of the circle
I'm already tired
So convenient at this time
No wonder Doraemon
is angry
My laziness is so hard to be cured
Need a lesson to recover
What?
Must be him,using weird machine
only Nobita Jian
Next time when I see him
I'll never forgive him
I know this is easy
but where are you going
That guy, I want to beat him up
(Winning the big prize)
Here is the news paper
I've been waiting
Today is the day announcing
lottery number
Where is the coupon
That's strange
These are the ones didn't win
You wasted 15000 Yen
He“.!
Honey
Don't be too much, you know?
Didn't you promise not to buy
any coupon
Ya, ya
That's why I didn't buy any
Just because I didn't buy any
That's why I didn't win any
Really?
These are the ones didn't win
What a pity
It's very hard to win lottery
If you already known that you'll
win, that's another story
30000000 Yen for one prize
third group 778631
It'd be nice to know the number
from the start
Use the time machine
Back to the time when buying the
coupons
No
You can't do that
WHY
Time machine can't be used to
make money
There's no law against that
That's no fun
Just once
No is no
Not to make money
just to get back what I loss
Just to win back the 50000 Yen
Hope they are selling the
winning one
See, the person is here
Actually, it's your greed
I want lottery coupon
Which one do you want?
The one that wins the lottery
How would I know
Just look at the paper
or 356,961
652...651
Don't have it here
Then, 4225 for 100000 Yen
Just one is fine
No, either
Then...
500000Yen or 1000000 Yen,
No ?
Can't buy it here
Didn't any winning ones
333333333...
300000000 Yen
Doraemon, what should I
do?
What should I say? Hurry and
buy it
But, didn't you say not to make
too much money
Never mind that, never mind that
I want this one
Forgot to bring money with me
Daddy, give me 100 Yen
Huff)'
Be polite
Thank you, bye
That one just sold out
Dorn. Who bought it?
No, maybe that's better
Using lottery to win money is wrong
One should work hard to make
money
That is true
Give it up. We don't have such
luck
Just one moment late, that means"
Only if we were one step earlier
It's daddy
Well...
Give me the 778631 of 3rd group
Daddy bought it 3 weeks ago
I wanted daddy to buy me 8
red bean cakes
Telescope, remote airplane, camera
and many other things
30000000 Yen
I want real pearl necklace
And he wants car, traveling overseas
New dress
And new furniture, and...
So many things I want
Honey
Oh, yes, buy you a new suit too
Then, I want
Wait, what are you talking about?
No use to hide it now
We saw you
Wait
I don't understand
HEY
Coupon
You won
What? You're talking about lottery
Don't worry about that
I thought I promised your mom
So, I sold it to a friend
Hey, you guys
I kept my promise and she's still
angry. What does that mean?
HQ-n!
Would you talk please
(Actual object solar camera)
This should be it
Really can take pictures ?
See
Really, what a pretty picture
Put the painting in the camera
Then use the sun light
And the picture is done
Can I borrow it
Sure
But only one film left
Know it? You need to be very
careful
Not done yet?
It should be it
No, it's not sun shinny day.
Have to wait for a while
No problem Take a look Look
Wonder if it's done
Ah, still kind of fuzzy
So, it's not done yet
See
So I was saying
That was the only I save since
kindergarten, the last one
How're you going to compensate
me?
It's not on the market any more
What should you do now ?
Oh, no
What? What has happened?
Listen to me everyone
Nobita
broke my important precious
It's Nobita again That rascle
Can't you do something
that can be proud of
What? What ?
Just for the sun light picure
and bully Nobita
Unforgivable
Don't cry
I'll give you something even better
So big What is this ?
This is the actual object sun light
camera
Stand in the front and don't move
then you can take the picture
All right, hurry
Don't move
ls it ready yet ?
This will take some time
Ok, you can move now
What a nice picture
Cool Big picture
There's something even more
surprising
It would be so horrible
It can take the picture of the house
You try it
How cute, really fun
Give this to Suneo, and he should be
satisfied
It would be a pity
but I can be proud then
You take the new sun light camera
to compensate me?
This is very special
I think you'll be happy about it
Take a picture now
It's real
As big as I am
More surprisingly
Just like real
Cool
You really want to give me this ?
Do you like it?
It's ok
Actually, I like the old one better
But I'll take this then
This is good for playing tricks
Suneo
Really
Why are you laying here?
How can you open eyes when
asleep
Answer me Suneo
The body is cold, not breathing
either
How can it be
Kill himself
He killed himself and died
I know it, must because I didn't
buy him things he wanted
If I knew it, I would have bought
him
Mom would buy you
Buy it for me
Ok, I'll buy whatever you want
So, don't kill yourself
go buy things you want
Suneo
What? This is just a doll
Playing tricks Too much
Jian
What?
That
Would you stand here please
Right here ?
Like this ?
Anything funny happen ?
Don't move please
Something funny is going to happen
Good, you can move now
Then see you later
What?
Nothing happened at all
Let me see
It's done now
Good
Hey, Jian
Let me be honest to you
I hate you the most
I want to revenge today, just be
aware
You always bully me
Dorn, what what
Monster Go somewhere else
Know how powerful I am now
Don't run Suneo
I'll not forgive you
I say stop
You bad boy
Don't run Suneo
So I say
Ole camera is better
Help
What is going on?
(News publisher Game)
Stop Nobita
What didn't you step on the ball
and slip
Why? I saw the ball
I threw the ball there
you should cooperate and slip
Don't be nonsense
Rascle
Dorn Jian
Ah? Ok, ok Take the picture
I'll never forgive Jian being so
violent
Come to think about it
I'm not as strong as he is
What are you looking at?
Suneo times
What is that?
Don't you know it
Suneo is publishing news paper
I heard he bought copy machine
Clumsy Nobita
Almost slip everyday
Finally reach his 1000 times
What a no good news, dorn
Hey, did you think the news
is funny?
So, Doraemon
I finally know
I'm sorry
I didn't know that
Ok! Pen against Violence
Since that
We can publish news paper too
Want to publish news paper
Publisher game tool
This is the reporter sign
and printer
Pull out the antena
see if anything happening
Put the sign on the head
Then the feet will move with it
Rush to the location and take
pictures
Picture and articles come out
at the same time
When Nobita's mom was taking
a nap a cockroach jumped into her mouth
If I put this on the news paper
mom will throw me out
ls it? Then don't use that one
Anyways, slow people like you
can publish news paper
Slow is the word wasted
I'm going out visiting
Go, go, go
Pull out the antena
Put on the sign
Rush to the location
It's basement of school
There's something happening
Anyways, take the picture and see
Let me see
5 babies were born at
school basement
It's not uncommon for cats to
do that
Good, it seems to be a big time
this time
What? Air plane crashed on the
field
This too exaggerated
This way? No, this way
Over there, this way
Where should I go ? I hate it
Isn't this Nobita?
Teacher
Why are you laying there ?
Come over here
Yes
How many time do I have to say
for you to study hard
What was the grade from last
test?
This camera is very strange
Push the button
the picture and article will come out
It shows
Nobita Yet always get zero from tests
You can use this report
Why can you write something
more like it
Inflation, bad economy...
What did the child just throw away?
Nobita Yet always gets zeros
from tests
Give it back to me
If you don't want it, then don't
throw it away
Did you collect any good news?
Put the picture and article here
The printer will print out paper
Not too exciting
Can't help it
No events around the area
Big news doesn't just happen
"Run the news"
Do you know what that means?
Don't just rely on the machine
Work hard to run the news
How horrible
Doraemon thinks he is
the head editor
Work hard to run the news?
It's Suneo
Good, I want to revenge
He'll throw the banana skin
on the ground
This a good opportunity
Someone is following me
It's Nobita
I was discovered
Nobita's 1001 times slip picture
I got it
You're so low Throwing the
banana skin everywhere
Not too smooth
The resource of news are too many
When luck goes bad
nothing good happens
ls there decisive blink moment?
Decisive blink moment
Have chance to revenge now
Follow him
will see him bully others
Then put it on the head line
The whole society will know
Everyone Can this thing be
allowed?
Sound so familiar
The book you're holding
looks very interesting
Let me see
Then he snatched
What? I've seen this before
Your airplane looks nice
let me see
This time must be it...
Have to do it like this to make it
fly high
Just wait and see
Thank you, big brother
Didn't know he can be so nice
What doesn't he do something
bad, I can't wait
Ah, Must be this time
It looks so delicious
But I have a bad tooth
Just a bad tooth
You can tolerate it
What? I thought something was
weird
Why are you following me?
That is because...no, no
Wow
Who can help me to take this
the decisive scenery
(Appraisal machine)
Too common
Change a posture
Look this way
Not too cute
Smile
Good, Lean backward
More, more
Don't be too much
Order me this and that
You're so nagging
Why do you want to paint
all of a sudden
We'll present our painting at
Shizuka's tomorrow
Jian and Suneo will be there too
Use the one you painted before
It won't work
Shizuka's uncle is coming
His uncle is...
How do I say that ?
That is called
Just the one watches paintings and
sculptures
And then critises proudly
And make money
Art critic
Right, that is it
The art critic is coming to
evaluate our painting
It's the chance for people to admit
that my painting is the best
Don't be lazy
hold your gesture now
I know
I have to be successful
Just like this, the second day
is coming
This painting is good
If focus more on the structure
would be even better
Please look at mine too
Let me see
You have improved Shizuka
But a bit messy
Put more effort to it, will be better
Uncle, my turn next
My painting is awful
In general
It's not a good one
But, how do you say it
It's quite spiriture
You have quality
If nourish properly
you should develop quite well
Really?
This painting looks pretty good
since you say that
I always think Suneo is quite talented
Please look at mine
Well
Any spirits
Young man
Did you paint this at the
kindergarten?
Nobita, don't cry
I understand you can't believe it
Anyway, someone appraised you
You have not comments then
Just like that
Bring me something for me to appraise
You're too practical
Critic machine
Even if a bad painting
it'll appraise it
Machine apprise you
Everyone will do the same
So easy ?
You don't believe
Let's try it out then
You draw a bad picture
Really bad
This painting is so bad
Let me look at the painting and
make critics
No, mom won't lie
Be honest will hurt your feeling
Ok, try it first
Look
Cool, so cool
Ah, what a nice painting
ls this really from Nobita?
Have to show it to your father
Honey
I don't want to see Nobita's
painting
I don't want to lie
Yet afraid of being honest
Genius, genius
Cool
this can only be describe as genius
I always dream about being a painter
Now, it seems Nobita can
make my dream come true
Isn't it too exaggerating ?
Possible
I'm going out now
Enjoy the appraisal
As long as you don't care if it's a lie
Saying my painting is from
kindergarten
Wait and see this time
How disgusting
No expanded feeling
Can't stand it
Isn't this small doll
The pink penther
where did you find this
Painting doll?
There's button on top of hat
You are drawing again?
Let me see, I want have a good
laugh at you
Wait and see, you'll be surprised
It's gone
Must drop it somewhere
Hurry and find it
Where is it?
Here? No, here? Here?
It's gone
Don't just stand there
A person can only look 3 minutes
Monalisa is not that great
Picasso can't compare with you
This is so touchy
This is real art
Please don't be standing there
Only 3 minutes a person
Can't not stand there
3 minutes a person please
There's along line behind
Please don't push
Cool, real genius
So touchable, genius
Genius, genius
(Skiing in the park)
I'm going to skiing
Well, it's going to be great
It's impossible to snow
People are so na?ve
We're flying over to see the sun
setting in Beihaido
There are a lot of snow
of course you can skiing there
I can train my skill there
I'll show you my picture
you guys just wait
How hateful
That's right
I don't care about Suneo
That's it
forget about Suneo
What? It's Suneo
I'm in the cabinet
I'm going to skiing now
The snow is great
Soft and light
You don't snow
guess you don't understand either
Dorn
Ok, I'll show him I want to
polish my skill at Beihaido too
You can't not skiing at all
So, I need to practice
Give me the Zonyimon
Can't use the tool just because of
some frustration
Don't you care I'll loss face
if I don't know how to skiing?
Space exchange machine
I have never used this before
Try this first
This is Space Exchanging Marker
Draw lines like this
Location is...
Pick somewhere near
Tatami is inside the circle
What is going on?
Come to the yard now
Exchange only the areas marked
Then, exchange part of here
with Beihaido
Try it now
Try to draw a big area
Put the map into the space exchanger
Beihaido is a big area
Only choose a small flat hill
turn on the power
This is the hill of Beihaido
Don't be like you used to be
Get tired easily
Of course
Then go for it
I'm going
It hurts
I have enough
Nobita
what are you doing up stairs
Why are you skiing inside
Mail this letter for me
I can't go mail the letter now
It hurts all over
Got it
exchange the location into pillar box
Do this first
Then set the neighborhood
Draw a exchange area
Find out the cigarette shop
Ok, here
Just great, pillar box
Good
You can go back now
This is wonderful
No matter where
When necessary
just exchange it here
This time
I want to go to the field
So, they are playing baseball
Where is here?
Not give you back the baseball
Ok, invite Shizuka over
Hey, Shizuka
Wherever you want to go
I can take you
Map of the world, I have them
I want to go there
Paris ? Sunset Avenue
Ok, come on
Only one tree from the sidewalk?
Can't help it
Can only move part of it
Amazon forest, a part of it
A part of Alvis top
Africa big prairie
It was close just now
Yes
exchange the beach of Hawaii
Good, I bring swimming suit
You give me one first
I thought you're
practicing skiing
Now, you mess up again
The room is too small
Bump into the wall all the time
It's true
Good, let exchange a big hill here
tonight
Where to?
Get up, I'll take you skiing
In the middle of night
Just because in the middle of night
we can exchange the hill
Where ?
In the park
No one is there at this hour
Hole the marker
Mark the park
Try to mark a big area
Turn on the power
The park has turned into a snow
mountain
A whole mountain
I want to make a snow man
All right
Skiing now
Why are you always falling down?
Doraemon, I think I'll wait
until my skill is better to practice
I'll practice
Don't be so strict
Help
We are lost, we can't go back now
It's all because of Suneo
saying skiing is fashionable
It's inhere from my parents to be
wanting face
If we don't; go back to Tokyo
I'll loss my job
Me too
I need to attend the PTA
I have to go to school too
Ah, cars coming
A taxi
There's a road
Stop, taxi
Take us to the cabinet
Cabinet?
This is a skiing field
Of course to the skiing cabinet
Skiing field? Where?
Beihaido snow mountain skiing field
Customer It takes a lot
of money to get there by taxi
I'm rich, hurry, hurry
I hate this, I have enough
You're too useless
Then change it back
Hurry, hurry
(The End)